- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
kids: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
孩子们：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
All:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
[flute plays]
[长笛演奏]
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[jaunty island music]
[欢快的岛屿音乐]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[模糊的喋喋不休]
- Jetsam City, here I come!
- 杰萨姆城，我来了！
This is going to be
the best weekend ever!
这将是
有史以来最好的周末！
[groans] Huh?
[呻吟]啊？
- Squidward.
- 章鱼哥。
- Bubble Bass.
- 泡泡鲈鱼。
- Don't tell me you're going
- 别告诉我你要走了
to the Jetsam City
comic convention too.
前往杰萨姆城
漫画大会也是如此。
- Oh, why would I waste my time
-哦，我为什么要浪费时间
on an idiotic comic book
convention?
在一本愚蠢的漫画书上
公约？
I am a man of sophistication.
我是一个老练的人。
I'm going to the
clarinet convention.
我要去
单簧管公约。
- Oh, please!
- 哦，拜托！
Talk about a waste of time.
谈论浪费时间。
- [growls] Shows what you know.
- [咆哮]展示你所知道的。
The lecture on the history
of spit valves
历史讲座
吐出阀数
is worth the price
of admission alone.
值得这个价钱
单独入场。
- When I said talk
about a waste of time,
- 当我说说话时
关于浪费时间，
I didn't mean literally.
我不是字面意思。
- Hmph!
——哼！
- All aboard for the train
to Jetsam City!
- 全部上车
前往杰萨姆城！
- Just stay away from me.
- 离我远一点。
- Dit to the O.
- 对 O 说。
[lively music]
[活泼的音乐]
[all clamoring]
[全都吵闹]
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
[groans]
Huh?
[呻吟]
啊？
Typical.
典型的。
Hmm...
- Dibs!
嗯...
- 迪布斯！
- [grumbles] Oh.
- [抱怨]哦。
[gasps]
[喘气]
- Keep walking, Bucko!
- 继续走，巴科！
- Oh, come on!
- 哦，来吧！
Oh!
哦！
Oh, you!
哦，你！
You're taking up two seats!
你占了两个座位！
- One for each cheek.
- 每脸颊各一个。
- Just move over!
- 走过去吧！
It's the last seat on the train.
这是火车上的最后一个座位。
- Oh, fine.
- 哦，好吧。
- And don't talk to me.
- 别跟我说话。
- Mmm!
- 嗯！
[slurping noisily]
[大声吸吮]
- [groans] It's finished!
- [呻吟]结束了！
- Hmph.
- 哼。
Then it appears
I need another snack.
然后出现
我还需要一份零食。
Huh?
啊？
[squeals]
The fondue cart!
[尖叫声]
火锅车！
- [yelps]
- The fondue cart!
- [尖叫声]
- 火锅车！
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- Fondue, sir?
- 火锅，先生？
- One bubbling bowl
of melted cheese, please.
- 一个冒泡的碗
请给我一些融化的奶酪。
- You're in luck, sir.
- 你很幸运，先生。
I just made a fresh,
piping hot batch!
我刚做了一个新鲜的，
滚烫的一批！
What size would you like?
您想要什么尺寸？
- Oh, I brought
my own fondue pot.
- 哦，我带来了
我自己的火锅锅。
Fill it to the rim.
将其填充至边缘。
- Yes, sir.
- 是的，先生。
- Uh, hey, hey.
Be-be-be careful with that!
- 呃，嘿，嘿。
小心一点！
- Next stop, Jetsam City!
- 下一站，杰萨姆城！
- [screams] Hot!
- [尖叫] 热！
- Are you going to eat that?
- 你要吃那个吗？
[slobbers noisily]
[大声流口水]
- Get off of me!
- 放开我！
- [snores]
- [打鼾]
- [groans] Hmph!
- [呻吟]哼！
[groans]
Stay on your side!
[呻吟]
留在你身边！
[growls]
[咆哮]
- Well, aren't you two
the best of friends!
- 好吧，你们两个不是吗？
最好的朋友！
- We are not!
- 我们不是！
Now, what do you want?
现在，你想要什么？
- Would you watch my baby
while I run to the restroom?
- 你会看管我的宝贝吗
当我跑去洗手间的时候？
I have to powder my nose
like a racehorse!
我得搽鼻粉
像赛马一样！
Thanks!
谢谢！
- [snores]
- [babbles]
- [打鼾]
- [胡言乱语]
- Ah!
- 啊！
- [wailing]
- [哀号]
- This is what I get
for traveling coach.
- 这就是我得到的
对于旅行教练。
- [snores]
- [打鼾]
That fondue gave me
the cheese sweats.
那火锅给了我
奶酪会出汗。
Oh! Refreshing.
哦！令人耳目一新。
- You're making the baby cold!
- 你让宝宝着凉了！
- [babbles]
- What?
- [胡言乱语]
- 什么？
Where did you get
such an adorable baby?
你从哪里得到的
这么可爱的宝宝？
Who clearly wants
the window open.
谁明确想要
窗户打开了。
- Oh!
- Huh?
- 哦！
- 啊？
- The baby wants it closed!
- 宝宝想要把它关上！
- The baby wants it open!
- 宝宝想要打开它！
- [babbles]
- Closed!
- [胡言乱语]
- 关门了！
- Open!
- Closed!
- 打开！
- 关门了！
- Open!
- 打开！
Both:
Huh? The baby!
两者：
啊？宝贝！
- I'm back!
- 我回来了！
Hey. Where's my baby?
嘿。我的宝贝在哪里？
- You really want to know?
- 你真的想知道吗？
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
- I hope she finds her baby.
- 我希望她找到她的孩子。
- Tickets! Tickets!
- 门票！门票！
Tickets?
门票？
[both chuckle]
[两人都笑了]
No tickets, huh?
没有门票吧？
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
- I loathe you.
- 我讨厌你。
- Don't you worry, baby.
- 别担心，宝贝。
When Mommy finds those two,
she's gonna ground them.
当妈妈找到那两个人时
她会把他们禁足的。
Into dust!
化为尘埃！
- I'm walking.
- 我正在走路。
- Without snacks?
- 没有零食吗？
I'm going to get hungry.
我要饿了。
You won't like me
when I'm hungry!
你不会喜欢我的
当我饿的时候！
- I don't like you now!
- 我现在不喜欢你了！
[bleak mellow music]
[凄凉柔和的音乐]
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
We're going to die out here!
我们会死在这里的！
[sobbing]
[bell ringing]
[抽泣]
[铃声响起]
- Huh? Maybe not. Look!
- 啊？也许不是。看！
♪ Old Man Jenkins has a farm ♪
♪ 詹金斯老人有一个农场 ♪
- ♪ And on that farm,
he has a ride? ♪
- ♪ 在那个农场里，
他有车吗？ ♪
Both:
♪ E-I-E-I-O! ♪
两者：
♪ 诶-我-我-我-欧！ ♪
- ♪ With a tractor here! ♪
- ♪ 这里有拖拉机！ ♪
- ♪ And some horsies there! ♪
- ♪ 那里还有一些马！ ♪
- ♪ Here a boat! ♪
- ♪ There a bike! ♪
- ♪ 这里有一艘船！ ♪
- ♪ 有一辆自行车！ ♪
- ♪ Everywhere
are boots to hike! ♪
- ♪ 无处不在
是徒步旅行的靴子！ ♪
- ♪ Old Man Jenkins
has a plane ♪
- ♪ 老詹金斯
有飞机♪
- ♪ E-I-E-I ♪
- ♪ 伊-伊-伊-我 ♪
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Quit it.
戒掉吧。
[airplane whirring]
[飞机呼呼]
- Thanks for the ride!
- 感谢您的搭车！
- And the egg salad sandwiches.
- 还有鸡蛋沙拉三明治。
- You folks are lucky!
- 你们真幸运！
I was just heading into the city
我刚刚进城
to pick up the new
Farmer's Almanac!
拿起新的
农民年鉴！
- To celebrate, I think
I will have another one
- 我想是为了庆祝
我再要一份
of those sandwiches.
那些三明治。
- Whoa! You just ate!
- 哇！你刚吃过饭！
- I can almost reach.
- 我几乎可以到达。
- Whoa!
- 哇！
- Stop shaking the plane
- 停止摇晃飞机
or I'll pull this thing
right over!
或者我会拉这个东西
结束了！
[both screaming]
[两人尖叫]
- Thank you. Much better.
- 谢谢。好多了。
[horn honks]
[喇叭鸣响]
- Now what do we do?
- 现在我们该怎么办？
- You could pull me using
the plane tail as a rickshaw.
- 你可以用
飞机尾部像人力车。
- Me pull you?
This is your fault!
- 我拉你吗？
这是你的错！
You should pull me!
你应该拉我！
- We'll flip a coin.
- 我们来抛一枚硬币。
- You're on!
- 你来了！
- Hmm?
- 唔？
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
I can't reach.
我够不到。
Could you fish it out?
你能把它捞出来吗？
- [groans] You win.
- [呻吟]你赢了。
[horn honks]
[喇叭鸣响]
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
[gloomy music]
[阴沉的音乐]
♪ ♪
Don't scratch the paint.
不要刮伤油漆。
- [chuckles]
- [轻笑]
Keep the change.
留着零钱吧。
[jaunty music]
[欢快的音乐]
[bell dinging]
[铃声]
- Yes?
- 是的？
- Reservation
for Squidward Tentacles.
- 预订
对于章鱼哥触手。
- And Bubble Bass.
- 还有泡泡鲈鱼。
- Mr. Tentacles and Mr. Bass.
- 触手先生和巴斯先生。
Ooh!
哦！
You two have reserved
our finest rooms.
你们两个已经预约了
我们最好的房间。
- Can we just get our keys?
- 我们能拿到钥匙吗？
- Mm, no.
- 嗯，不。
You were supposed to
check in yesterday.
你本来应该
昨天入住。
But you didn't.
但你没有。
So we gave your rooms away.
所以我们把你的房间给了。
[both sobbing]
[两人都抽泣]
[groans]
Let me see what we can do.
[呻吟]
让我看看我们能做什么。
Oh! Here we go.
哦！开始了。
Though it's not as nice as
your previous accommodations.
虽然它不如
您以前的住宿。
- [sniffles]
- It's just for one night.
- [抽鼻子]
- 只住一晚。
How bad can it be?
有多糟糕？
Say, this isn't so bad.
说吧，这还不算太糟糕。
- The shower's all yours.
- 淋浴间都是你的了。
- [groans] I'm tired.
I'm just going to sleep.
- [呻吟]我累了。
我要睡觉了。
- As you wish.
- 如你所愿。
Ah!
- [grunts]
啊!
- [咕哝]
- Hey, keep to your side.
- 嘿，留在你身边。
- [grumbles]
- [抱怨]
[crunching]
Huh?
[嘎吱嘎吱]
啊？
Oh, you're getting crumbs
in the bed!
哦，你得到了面包屑
在床上！
I'm going to sleep
in the bathroom.
我要睡觉了
在浴室里。
Hmph!
哼！
- Suit yourself.
- 适合你自己。
- What?
- 什么？
Of course he destroyed
the bathroom.
他当然毁掉了
浴室。
But hey, this is fancy.
但是嘿，这太奇特了。
Shag carpeting!
粗毛地毯！
- ♪ That's not carpet ♪
- ♪ 那不是地毯 ♪
[shrieking]
[尖叫]
- Is this your body hair?
- 这是你的体毛吗？
What is wrong with you?
你怎么了？
The horror.
恐怖。
[gloomy music]
[阴沉的音乐]
[foghorn blares]
[雾号声]
- Well, you look chipper.
- 嗯，你看起来精神抖擞。
Did you sleep well?
- Nope!
你睡的好吗？
- 没有！
But soon you'll be
at your lame comic convention,
但很快你就会
在你蹩脚的漫画大会上，
far away from me!
离我远点！
That is something
to smile about.
那是某事
微笑着。
- Agreed.
- 同意。
But your Clarinet Con is,
by far, the lamer of the two.
但你的单簧管演奏会是，
到目前为止，两者中较弱的一个。
- Yay!
- 耶！
Comic books!
漫画书！
[groans]
[呻吟]
- Well, at least we clarinetists
- 好吧，至少我们单簧管演奏家
don't wear stupid capes.
不要穿愚蠢的斗篷。
[jaunty clarinet melody]
[欢快的单簧管旋律]
- [grunts, groans]
- [咕哝声，呻吟声]
- You were saying?
- 你是说？
Yoo-hoo-hoo!
- [laughs]
哟呼呼！
- [笑]
Whoa!
哇！
- Whoa!
- 哇！
- Is that...
[airplane whirring]
- 那是...
[飞机呼呼]
Old Man Jenkins?
老詹金斯？
- Gadzooks!
- 小玩意儿！
[people screaming]
[人们尖叫]
- No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- 不，不，不，不，不，不，
不，不，不，不，不，不，不！
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
- No, no, no, no, no, no!
- 不，不，不，不，不，不！
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
[jaunty music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
Any landing you can walk
away from is a good landing!
您可以步行的任何着陆点
远离是很好的登陆！
[people scream]
[人们尖叫]
- No!
- 不！
All those innocent
comic books, lost!
所有那些无辜的人
漫画，丢了！
- Ha! In your face!
- 哈！当着你的面！
I still get to go
to my clarinet convention,
我还是得走了
参加我的单簧管大会，
and you get nothing!
而你什么也得不到！
You lose!
你输了！
[laughs]
[笑]
[people screaming]
[人们尖叫]
- Of course.
- 当然。
- Worst. Trip.
- 最糟糕的。旅行。
- Ever!
- 曾经！
Hey, where did everybody go?
嘿，大家都去哪儿了？
[train horn blaring]
[火车喇叭鸣响]
both:
The train station!
两者：
火车站！
[indistinct chatter]
[模糊的喋喋不休]
- No tickets, no ride.
- 没有门票，不能乘车。
Both:
Huh?
两者：
啊？
- You boys owe me half a plane!
- 你们孩子们欠我半架飞机！
- Typical.
- 典型的。
[groans]
- Slow down!
[呻吟]
- 慢点！
You're hurting my arms!
你弄疼我的胳膊了！
- There they are, Junior!
Both: Huh?
- 他们在那里，少年！
两人：啊？
[both panting]
[两人都气喘吁吁]
- After 'em!
- 追随他们！
Both:
I loathe you, chum!
两者：
我讨厌你，伙计！
[growl]
[咆哮]
[scream]
[尖叫]
[jaunty island music]
[欢快的岛屿音乐]
♪ ♪
- I have put off cleaning
my attic for way too long.
- 我推迟了清洁工作
我的阁楼已经呆得太久了。
[gasps]
Aww!
[喘气]
哇！
Gary's baby shell!
加里的婴儿壳！
They grow up so fast.
他们长得真快。
[groaning]
[呻吟]
Hey!
嘿！
My imagination box!
我的想象力盒子！
I wonder if it still works.
我想知道它是否仍然有效。
Oh, boy, it's time for...
噢，孩子，是时候...
imagination!
想像力！
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
Whee-hee!
嘿嘿！
[engine grinding]
[发动机磨削]
That's weird.
这很奇怪。
- Hey, neighbor.
- 嘿，邻居。
Can I borrow a cup of sand?
我可以借一杯沙子吗？
I'm all out.
我已经全部出局了
Huh?
啊？
Hey!
Isn't that the...?
嘿！
这不是那个……吗？
- It is!
But it won't start.
- 这是！
但它不会开始。
- Oh.
- 哦。
Let me see
if I can get it going.
让我看看
如果我能做到的话。
[engine grinding]
[发动机磨削]
[wheezing]
[喘息]
- We need a professional.
- 我们需要一个专业人士。
Imagination Box Repair.
想象力盒子修复。
This is the place!
就是这个地方！
- Ooh!
- 哦！
Aha!
啊哈！
Ooh.
哦。
Welcome!
欢迎！
[fireworks bursting]
[烟花爆竹]
Wow, a double corrugated 3600.
哇，双瓦楞3600。
I haven't seen one
of these in 25 years.
我还没见过一个
25 年内。
What seems to be the problem?
似乎有什么问题？
- Well, the inspiration motor
won't turn over.
- 嗯，灵感马达
不会翻身。
Dern thing's on the fritz.
Dern 的事情很麻烦。
- Yeah. And it doesn't work.
- 是的。但这不起作用。
- Hmm.
- 唔。
Let me take a look
under the flap.
让我看看
在皮瓣下。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[metallic clanking]
[金属叮当声]
[gurgles]
[咯咯声]
Well, there's your problem.
嗯，这就是你的问题。
Your box has blown
a whimsy gasket.
你的盒子炸了
一个异想天开的垫圈。
They don't make those anymore!
他们不再做那些了！
But I could give you
a great deal on a cushion fort.
但我可以给你
坐垫堡垒上有很多东西。
- No, that's okay.
- 不，没关系。
I'm a cardboard man.
我是一个纸板人。
- Aw, this dumb ol' box
is just junk now.
- 噢，这个愚蠢的盒子
现在只是垃圾。
- Hey! Get off my sand!
- 嘿！离开我的沙子！
[grumbles] Whoa!
[抱怨]哇！
[thumping, yelling]
[重击，大喊]
What's happening?
发生什么事了？
Where am I?
我在哪里？
- Inside my imagination box.
- 在我的想象力盒子里。
- Where'd he go?
- 他去哪儿了？
- You must have jostled
something and fixed it.
- 你一定是撞到了
某事并修复它。
[gasps]
[喘气]
Patrick!
Squidward must be lost!
帕特里克！
章鱼哥一定会迷失的！
- Lost in his own...
- 迷失在自己的...
both:
Imagination!
两者：
想象力！
- [groans] I can't
see a thing in here!
- [呻吟]我不能
看到这里有东西！
I need a flashlight!
我需要一个手电筒！
- Just imagine a flashlight.
- 想象一下手电筒。
- Oh, yeah, right.
- 哦，是的，对。
I'll just imagine it
and it'll appear!
我只会想象一下
它就会出现！
[grumbles]
[抱怨]
What the...
什么...
oh, it worked.
哦，成功了。
Now, where's the way
out of here?
现在，路在哪里
离开这里？
Ooh! I'm leaving!
哦！我要走了！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Huh?
啊？
[screaming]
[尖叫]
How do I get out
of this crazy place?
我怎样才能出去
这个疯狂的地方？
- That's easy, Squidward.
- 这很简单，章鱼哥。
Just visualize
where you'd rather be!
只是想象一下
你想去的地方！
- I'd rather be
far away from you!
- 我宁愿是
离你远点！
Like at a fancy beach resort.
就像在一个豪华的海滩度假村。
[mellow island music]
【柔和的岛屿音乐】
[gasps]
[喘气]
And relaxing on a lounge chair.
并在躺椅上放松。
Ooh!
哦！
Ahh, sipping a tropical drink.
啊，喝着热带饮料。
Ahh.
啊。
Maybe this imagination thing
isn't so bad after all.
或许这就是想象力
毕竟没那么糟糕。
- What are you doing now?
- 你在干什么？
- Well, if you must know,
I'm relaxing
- 好吧，如果你一定要知道的话，
我很放松
under an umbrella surrounded
by beautiful tropical plants.
被包围的伞下
由美丽的热带植物组成。
- Sounds like
you're in a jungle.
- 听起来像
你在丛林里。
- No!
- 不！
It's not a... jungle?
这不是……丛林？
- [shrieks, grumbles]
- [尖叫，抱怨]
- Aren't jungles full
of dangerous animals?
- 丛林不是满了吗
危险的动物？
- Yep!
Like scary sea snakes!
- 是的！
就像可怕的海蛇一样！
- Huh?
- 啊？
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- [hissing]
- [嘶嘶声]
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
Hey! You gotta help me!
嘿！你得帮帮我！
- Oh, and look out
for sea panthers.
-哦，小心
对于海豹来说。
- [growls, roars]
- [咆哮，咆哮]
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
[whimpering]
[呜咽]
- [growls]
- [hisses]
- [咆哮]
- [嘶嘶声]
- How's it going
in there, Squidward?
- 怎么样
在那里，章鱼哥？
- You're making
everything worse!
- 你正在做
一切都更糟！
Would you two clam up?
你们两个能闭嘴吗？
- Oh, I forgot to mention
the clothes-eating clams.
-哦，我忘记说了
吃衣服的蛤
- [chomps]
- [screams] Giant clam!
- [咀嚼]
- [尖叫] 巨蛤！
[screams]
Let go! Ow! Ouch!
[尖叫声]
放开！噢！哎哟!
Hey, that's my shirt!
嘿，那是我的衬衫！
Oh, fantastic!
哦，太棒了！
Now I'm lost in the jungle
with no clothes on.
现在我迷失在丛林里
没穿衣服。
- That's no problem.
- 那没问题。
Remember, you can
imagine anything!
请记住，你可以
想象任何事情！
- Imagine, huh?
- 想象一下吧？
All right.
[grunting]
好的。
[咕噜声]
Oh, not bad.
哦，还不错。
A jungle safari could be fun.
丛林探险可能会很有趣。
- Oh!
- 哦！
And whatever you do,
don't imagine...
而且无论你做什么，
不要想象...
a stampede of sea elephants!
海象的踩踏！
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
[elephant trumpeting]
[大象的喇叭声]
- Thanks a lot!
- 多谢！
- No problem!
- 没问题！
- Now tell me how to escape
from a stampede
- 现在告诉我如何逃脱
来自踩踏事件
of sea elephants!
- Hmm.
海象！
- 唔。
If only you had
a hot air balloon.
如果你有
一个热气球。
- [elephants trumpeting]
- [大象吹号]
- Huh?
- 啊？
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- Huh?
- 啊？
- [laughing]
- [screaming]
- [笑]
- [尖叫]
[screaming continues]
[尖叫声继续]
- I've always wanted
to ride in a balloon.
-我一直想要
乘坐气球。
- Me too!
- 我也是！
Unless there's a tornado.
除非有龙卷风。
- Tornado?
- 龙卷风？
[wind blowing]
[风吹来]
- [laughing]
- [screaming]
- [笑]
- [尖叫]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
- You know what's better
than a tornado?
- 你知道什么是更好的
比龙卷风？
A bubble tornado!
泡沫龙卷风！
- Huh?
- 啊？
Huh?
啊？
Ahh.
啊。
[yelps]
[尖叫声]
- You okay, Squidward?
- 你还好吗，章鱼哥？
- No!
- 不！
- He's okay.
- 他没事。
- Say, are there dinosaurs
in the jungle?
- 说，有恐龙吗
在丛林里？
- Oh, no.
- 哦，不。
[shrieking, roaring]
[尖叫、咆哮]
[yelling]
[大喊]
I hate imagination!
我讨厌想象力！
- [roars]
- [咆哮]
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
- I'm so happy
Squidward's having
- 我很高兴
章鱼哥有
such an exciting adventure!
如此令人兴奋的冒险！
- How do I get out
of this jungle?
- 我怎么出去
这片丛林的？
- Hmm.
- 唔。
Try imagining
your favorite place!
尝试想象一下
你最喜欢的地方！
- Favorite place?
Um, I've got it!
- 最喜欢的地方？
嗯，我明白了！
A jazz club!
爵士俱乐部！
[soft jazz music playing]
[轻柔的爵士乐演奏]
♪ ♪
Ooh, finally.
哦，终于。
A place with culture.
一个有文化的地方。
[sniffs] Ahh.
[吸鼻子] 啊。
Even the coffee
smells like jazz.
就连咖啡
闻起来像爵士乐。
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Digging that groove.
挖那个沟。
Both:
We dig it!
两者：
我们挖它！
[imitating guitar wailing]
[模仿吉他哀嚎]
- [grumbling]
- [抱怨]
[disquieting music]
[令人不安的音乐]
Ugh!
This coffee tastes like rocks!
啊!
这咖啡尝起来像石头！
[rock chord plays]
[yelps]
[摇滚和弦演奏]
[尖叫声]
- One, two, three, four!
- 一、二、三、四！
- Punk rock?
- 朋克摇滚？
- [giggling]
- [咯咯笑]
- [screams]
Everything's gone crazy!
- [尖叫]
一切都变得疯狂了！
- Sounds like your
imagination is overheating.
- 听起来像你的
想象力过热。
Try to clear your mind.
试着理清思绪。
- Clear my mind?
Clear my mind!
- 清除我的思绪？
理清我的思绪！
Phew!
唷！
- Where are you now, Squidward?
- 你现在在哪里，章鱼哥？
- I'm in an empty white void.
- 我身处一片白色的虚空之中。
But at least it's peaceful.
但至少是平静的。
- Uh, that sounds like
the Doodle dimension.
- 呃，听起来像是
涂鸦维度。
- Watch out for DoodleBob!
- 小心涂鸦鲍勃！
- What's he look like?
- 他长什么样？
- Um, he looks
kind of like this.
- 嗯，他看起来
有点像这样。
- [gibbering]
- [胡言乱语]
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
[screaming]
[尖叫]
Would somebody please...
[grunts]
有人请...
[咕哝]
Tell me how...
[grunts]
告诉我怎么...
[咕哝]
To get out of this...
[grunts]
为了摆脱这个...
[咕哝]
Stupid box!
[groans]
傻盒子！
[呻吟]
- You want out?
- 你想出去吗？
- Well, why didn't you say so?
- 那么，你为什么不这么说呢？
Just draw an exit door.
只需画一个出口门即可。
- I don't have a pen!
- 我没有笔！
- You're an octopus.
You're full of ink!
- 你是章鱼。
你满身都是墨水！
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
- [gibbering]
- [胡言乱语]
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
Huh? Huh?
啊？啊？
I'm home!
我到家了！
[sobs]
[抽泣]
Hmph.
哼。
Where did SpongeBob
and Patrick run off to?
海绵宝宝去哪儿了
和帕特里克跑去？
Oh, well.
那好吧。
I'm going to the place
where imagination goes to die.
我要去那个地方
想象力将消亡。
My dreary, pointless
minimum wage job.
我的沉闷、毫无意义
最低工资工作。
[inhales] Ah, the good old
boring Krusty Krab.
[吸气]啊，老好人
无聊的蟹堡王。
I'm actually happy to be back.
我真的很高兴能回来。
May I take your order, sir?
先生，我可以接受您的命令吗？
- Should we tell him?
- 我们应该告诉他吗？
- Nah, he sounds so happy.
- 不，他听起来很高兴。
- One Krabby combo coming up!
- 一款蟹蟹组合即将推出！
[sighs]
[叹气]
[mellow island music]
【柔和的岛屿音乐】
♪ ♪